What is it about reunions that make some people reluctant to go to?
是什么让一些人不愿意参加重聚活动呢？
Is it that they're afraid of being judged by people who they met in their heyday?
是因为他们害怕被那些在自己鼎盛时期结识的人评判吗？
Is it a fear of having betrayed high expectations?
是担心辜负了人们的高期望吗？
Or is it the risk of realising that the sparkle that held the group together is no longer there?
还是害怕意识到曾经将大家凝聚在一起的那种闪光点已经不复存在了呢？
Fans have been keen on a Spice Girls reunion, but Posh Spice is saying 'no'.
粉丝们一直渴望辣妹合唱团重组，但是“优雅辣妹”却表示拒绝。
Fans have eagerly followed months of speculation about the five British singers getting together again.
粉丝们热切关注了数月来有关这五位英国歌手再次聚首的各种猜测。
For this generation - now mainly middle aged mothers - it's a chance to introduce the band to their own daughters.
对于这一代人——现在主要是中年妈妈们——这是一个向自己女儿介绍这个乐队的机会。
But, unfortunately, it's not gonna happen.
但不幸的是，这不会发生了。
They might see four of them.
她们或许只能看到其中四位成员。
The spoil sport seems to be Victoria Beckham.
扫兴的人似乎是维多利亚·贝克汉姆。
Maybe Posh Spice became too posh herself to shake her booty on a stage.
也许“优雅辣妹”变得太过高雅，以至于不愿意在舞台上扭动屁股了。
She's said in the past that she's got no plans to join with Baby, Scary, Ginger and Sporty.
她过去曾表示，她没有计划与“宝贝辣妹”“疯狂辣妹”“姜汁辣妹”和“运动辣妹”重聚。
"Doing the Olympics was an incredible honour.
“能够在奥运会上表演是一项难以置信的荣誉。
That's great.
那很棒。
Thank you to everybody, but no more," she said after the group performed at the closing ceremony of the Olympic Games in London in 2012.
感谢每一个人，但不会再有下一次了。”2012年，辣妹合唱团在伦敦奥运会闭幕式上表演后，她这样说道。
And then there's Friends.
然后就是《老友记》。
Well, no more chats at the (fictitious) Central Perk cafe for Chandler Bing.
嗯，钱德勒·宾再也不会在（虚构的）中央公园咖啡馆里聊天了。
Actor Matthew Perry has announced that he won't attend the reunion show of the hit American TV sitcom which captured the imagination of audiences in several countries.
演员马修·派瑞已经宣布，他不会参加这部曾吸引了多个国家观众的热门美国电视情景喜剧的重聚节目。
It ended in 2004 after ten series.
这部剧在播出十季后于2004年完结。
Perry's spokesperson said he "may tape something" as a tribute to the series' creator James Burrows but... he is otherwise engaged.
派瑞的发言人表示，他“可能会录制一些东西”作为致敬礼物给该剧的创作者詹姆斯·伯罗斯，但是……
As some Hollywood actors do, he will star in a play in London which runs until May.
他要参与其他工作。和一些好莱坞演员一样，他将在伦敦主演一部持续到五月的戏剧。
It's a story about being middle aged.
这是一个关于中年生活的故事。
Enough said.
无需多言了。